<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Food Menu App</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="large_text">
        "<u><b>COMPANY'S PROFILE</b></u>\n\n"
        "<b>Ambience</b> \n\n"
        "This is a perfect location and no matter the occasion,   you are guaranteed a unique dining experience.\n"
        "Whether you are after an intimate dinner for two or a private party, we cater for all.\n"
        "We boasts a separate Bollywood function room with a seating capacity for up to 40 people.\n"
        "The Bollywood room has its own bar and sound system so you can enjoy a truly sensational and private event.\n\n\n"

        "<b>Menu</b> \n\n"
        "We also boasts an innovative menu, which is prepared with only the freshest and finest ingredients. \n"
        "It has a comprehensive menu with a variety of vegetarian, meat and fish dishes.\n"
        "The menu caters for all palettes with its offer of a variety of traditional and contemporary Indian cuisine.\n"
        "All our dishes are prepared with a genuine passion for creating authentic and mouth-watering food.\n\n\n"

        "If you have a sweet tooth, then you are in for a real treat. Not only do we offer home favourites such as ras malai, we also have 10 varieties of Movenpick Swiss Ice Cream.\n\n\n"

        "The kitchen staff here available are amongst the finest, bringing with them experiences from cooking in five star restaurants in India.\n"
        "We are also pleased to have the Head chef and pioneer for the much loved menu at Sheesh Mahal join our team.\n\n"
        "A full take away menu is available, for collection only.\n\n\n\n"
        "-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_locate_us">Map</string>
</resources>
